SHADI **SHOMALI**

Maeen st. Marj el Hamam, Amman · 0797277439 shadishomali97@gmail.com · www.shadishomali.com

Outgoing Computer Science student at Princess Sumayya University of Technology with a +2 years' experience as a freelancer full stack web developer. Seeking to leverage my technical and professional expertise to grow in the new role of Intern at your company.

EXPERIENCE

2018 - PRESENT

JR. WEB DEVELOPER, INSPIROM

Developing and sketching client's thoughts into a website with a full responsibility and a direct contact with the client until project deadline.

2017 - PRESENT

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER, FREELANCER

Developing client's ideas into a website, whether it's a business directory, E-commerce or informational websites.

2013 - 2016

SALESMAN, SAHOURY UNIFORM

Contracting with local schools for uniforms.

EDUCATION

PRESENT

UNDERGRADUATE OF BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, PRINCESS SUMAYYA UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

4'th year

JANUARY - 2019

BLOCKCHAIN - HYPERLEDGER FABRIC FULL COURSE, UDEMY

LEARNING INTRODUCTORY TOPICS OF HYPERLEDGER DEVELOPMENT SUCH AS SETTING HYPERLEDGER ENVIROMENT AND DEPLOYING HYPERLEDGER NETWORK FOR FRONT END APPLICATIONS.

NOVEMBER - 2018

INTRODUCTION TO BLOCKCHAIN - ETHEREUM, UDEMY

LEARNED BASIC TOPICS OF BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPMENT SUCH AS SETTING ENVIROMENT, BASICS OF SOLIDITY LANGUAGE AND DEPLOYING SMART CONTRACTS.

MARCH 2017

CCNA ROUTING AND SWITCHING INTRODUCTORY WORKSHOP, PIONEERS

ACADEMY

8 hours introductory course of CCNA to expand my knowledge and learn to implement local networks

JULY - 2017

WEB DEVELOPMENT SUMMER TRAINING, RELEANS ACADEMY

LEARNED BASIC TOPICS OF WEB DEVELOPMENT SUCH AS; HTML5, CSS, JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP, MYSQL, PHP MVC, OOP AND YII2 FRAMEWORK.

MAY - 2015

JORDANIAN TAWJIHI SCIENTIFIC STREAM, AMMAN BAPTIST SCHOOL

JUNF - 2011

DIPLÔME D'ÉTUDES EN LANGUE FRANÇAISE (DELF) A1 LEVEL, INSTITUT FRANCAIS DE JORDANIE

SKILLS

- Good level dealing with data structures and algorithms.
- Tools: Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, Apache Server, Wamp32, Eclipse IDE, VS Code, Sublime Text 3, PyCharm, Visual Studio, NetBeans.
- Programming Languages:
 C++, C#, JAVA, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS,
 PHP, NodeJS, GO Programming, Python.
- Flexibility and tolerance.
- Outgoing and energetic attitude.
- Fast self-learner.
- Multi-tasking abilities.

ACTIVITIES

MARCH - 2019

CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION IN MODEL UNITED NATIONS CONFRENCE 2019

Participated as an Admin Staff in the 8th annual Princess Sumayya University for Technology Model United Nations Conference.

SEPTEMBER - 2018

VOLUNTEERED TO DEVELOP THE PRINCES SUMAYYA UNIVERSITY FOR TECHNOLOGY MODEL UNITED NATIONS WEBSITE

JULY - 2018

VOLUNTEERED AS A SKATING COACH IN TAJ MALL, WORLD OF SKATING

Developing client's ideas into a website, whether it's a business directory, E-commerce or informational websites.

MARCH - 2016

CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION IN MODEL UNITED NATIONS CONFRENCE 2016

Participated as a Delegate in the 4th annual Princess Sumayya University for Technology Model United Nations Conference.

PROJECTS

PRESENT

DEVELOPED TRAVELING AGENCY WEBSITE, WWW.EMILIO-JO.COM

Designed and Developed Emilio Traveling Agency official website.

2019

DEVELOPED VAPENJI WEBSITE, WWW.VAPENJI.NET

Designed and Developed Vapenji | Online Vape Shop E-commerce website using Wordpress technology.

2019

DEVELOPED SOLOSOUND WEBSITE, WWW.SOLOSOUNDJO.COM

Designed and Developed SoloSound website.

2019

DEVELOPED INSPIROM WEBSITE, WWW.INSPIROM.NET

Designed and Developed Inspirom – marketing agency website.

2018

DEVELOPED TODAY CHOCOLATE WEBSITE, WWW.TODAYCHOCOLATE.COM

Designed and Developed Today Chocolate Official website.

2018

SYSTEM ANALYSIS AND DESIGN FOR ONLINE BUS TRACKING SYSTEM

Designed and Analyzed a complete integrated system and implemented the database design for the system.

2018

DEVELOPED A SMALL PAINT PROJECT USING ASSEMBLY LANGUAGE

A similar windows paint application using Intel 8086 Interrupts Architecture.

2018

DEVELOPED BUBBLE SHOOTING GAME USING ASSEMBLY LANGUAGE

Using Intel 8086 Interrupts Architecture.

2018

CREATED A COURSE REGISTERING SYSTEM USING MYSQL

MySQL based database with PHP as the back-end for the system and Bootstrap for the front-end and tested using Apache.

2018

DEVELOPED A CAR RENTING WEBSITE

Car renting website using an application form sent by mail to assign rent details and for the front end it's designed using Bootstrap.

2017

DEVELOPED SNAKE GAME USING C# LANGUAGE

2016

DEVELOPED A SLOTMACHINE APPLICATION USING JAVA PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

By using Java GUI for the interface of the desktop application.